Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Hans Weissenstein Negatives PHOTOS 019 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administration and Services.
  - Headquarters & HS Equivalency Course, 4 Classes, Jul 9, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14410)
- Series II: Ceremonies.
  - Teachers' Guild Hotel Astor [Dewey Luncheon], undated (Box 1, Item 112)
  - Teachers' Guild Dinner Hotel Roosevelt, Jan 25, 1953 (Box 1, Item 960)
  - Teachers' Guild Hotel Olcott [luncheon], Nov 13, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1492)
  - Teachers' Guild 25th Anniversary dinner Hotel Roosevelt, Mar 5, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1726)
  - Teachers' Guild Roosevelt Hotel - Awards Luncheon & Panel (George Counts & John Childs Dewey Awards), Mar 5, 1955 (Box 1, Item 2292)
  - Teachers' Guild [Abe] Lefkowitz dinner Hotel Commodore, May 23, 1955 (Box 1, Item 2436)
  - Teachers' Guild Check presentation [Charles] Cogen, Dec 6, 1955 (Box 1, Item 2675)
  - Teachers' Guild Spring Luncheon Walter Reuther & George Meany, Mar 3, 1956 (Box 1, Item 2877)
  - C[ogen, Charles?] K[olodny, Jules?] City Hall Teacher Presentations, May 21, 1957 (Box 1, Item 3617)
  - C[ogen, Charles?] K[olodny, Jules?] March of Dimes PS 54 check presentation, Jan 31, 1958 (Box 1, Item 3981)
  - Spring Luncheon, Mar 4, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6224)
  - Raffle Drawing (Teacher Recognition Day) ["Teachers will be recognized when they achieve collective bargaining status" sign hanging on podium.], May 16, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6370)
  - Spring Luncheon Commodore Hotel Secretary of Labor Goldberg, Mar 3, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6898)
  - AFT Luncheon & Awards, Journalistic, Aug 19, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7817)
  - Check pres[entation] Cogen, Selden, Aeberman [?], Jan 7, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8059)
  - Check Presentation office - Albert Shanker - [Charles] Cogen, Apr 15, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8248)
  - Board of Education [Robert] Atkin[s] Swearing-in, May 25, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8339)
  - Swearing in Officers Marc Ballroom, Jun 10, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8431)
  - 5 yrs. Network Strike party Hilton, Nov 5, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9382)
  - Mayor's Committee on scholastic achievement 4 Seasons [awards ceremony], Dec 8, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9456)
  - Community Celebration PS 113 Percy Sutton, Jun 16, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10572)
  - Library Dedication, Jun 21, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10585)
  - AFT Million Dollar ["Million Dollar Militancy Fund"] Dinner for Jailbirds, May 29, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11251)
  - Check presentation, Nov 12, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11489)
  - Swearing in Dave Wittes, May 12, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11861)
  - Board of Education Gladys Roth Award, May 22, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11904)
  - District 28 Albert Shanker Man of the Year, May 23, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11895)
  - Presentation Sheepshead Bay, Jun 6, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11943)
  - Dante's Restaurant - Para-Professional, Jun 6, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11941)
  - Dedication, Jun 12, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11966)
  - PS 211Bronx Dedication Bi-lingual, Sep 11, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12038)
  - [Al] Shanker Reception Bronx, Oct 31, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12132)
  - Albert Shanker reception Brooklyn, Nov 13, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12193)
  - Queens reception [Al] Shanker, Nov 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12214)
  - G.E. check presentation, Nov 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12213)
  - Al] Shanker reception George Washington Hotel, Dec 4, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12251)
  - [Al] Shanker Dinner, Dec 15, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12282)
  - [$]40,000 for GE workers, Dec 17, 1969 (Box 10, Item 12293)
  - Art Show Winners Madison Square Garden, Jan 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12321)
  - Party in Brooklyn, Caterers, Jan 14, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12330)
  - Regent Scholars at Fordham, Feb 6, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12381)
  - [Abe] Lefkowitz Library Dedication, Feb 16, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12395)
  - Brock Peters Awards IS 10 ["Welcome Home Brock Peters" sign; actor Brock Peters comes back to his old school[?]], Mar 6, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12425)
  - Colloquia & Reception [all members have name plaques], Mar 20, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12451)
  - Reception & Luncheon, Mar 21, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12453)
  - Reception Greek Freedom Fighters Central Labor Council, Mar 26, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12474)
  - PS 274 Weatherless - St. Moritz [(UFT members from PS 274?) at event at St. Moritz Hotel in Manhattan that appears to honor an elderly woman wearing a hat, possibly surnamed "Weatherless."], Apr 11, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12501)
  - Retirement Teachers Luncheon Grand St. Boys Club, May 12, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12581)
  - Queens Jamaica PS[?] Dedication, May 15, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12589)
  - Albert Shanker jail release & reception, May 29, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12629)
  - Candello Party, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12674)
  - Mini School Opening Dedication PS 134, Jun 12, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12675)
  - Headstart Anniversary Flushing, Jun 13, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12678)
  - Luncheon, Jun 29, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12699)
  - Little Red School Middle School Opening, Sep 30, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12790)
  - District 20 Brooklyn, Scholarship Party, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13013)
  - Scholarship Awards Fordham University, Feb 26, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13104)
  - IS 162 Bronx New School Opening, Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13218)
  - Spring Conference Display - Sessions - Awards (1st Day), Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13221)
  - PS 104 Bronx Opening of annex, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13259)
  - Ted Britton Dinner - Hilton Dinner, May 1, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13257)
  - Retired Teachers lunch, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13285)
  - Bronx Day, May 12, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13290)
  - Leichter Party District 20 La Mere, May 18, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13312)
  - Julia Richmond HS $12,000 check Football Team, May 20, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13324)
  - Manhattan Boro office 1 yr., May 21, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13323)
  - PS 23 Mini School Opening Ribbon Cutting, Jun 2, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13366)
  - 300 Scholarships at Julia Richmond [?], Jun 8, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13384)
  - PS 128 Bronx District Show Awards & Exhibit, Jun 9, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13389)
  - Early - childhood luncheon - La Bibliotheque, Jun 19, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13411)
  - PS 169 Awards, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13429)
  - Assigned Teacher Swear in, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13425)
  - IRS [IS?] 218 Scholarships, Jun 24, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13433)
  - Bushwick HS Graduation Brooklyn - UFT Scholarship Awards (RKO Madison Theater), Jun 28, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13434)
  - Prospect Heights HS Brooklyn Federal School Summer Program Awards, Aug 12, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13455)
  - New York Hilton Haaren HS Mini School Luncheon [Haaren HS, located at 10th Ave between 58th and 59th streets, closed in the late 1970's.], Aug 17, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13457)
  - IS 102 Bronx "Teacher of Year", Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13512)
  - Award to Teacher of the Year Long Island, Oct 28, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13571)
  - Teachers of Year, Board of Education, [Carol] Landau / Frudland, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13586)
  - Teacher of the Year Paul Gershwin[?], Bronx, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13575)
  - Anniversary of School PS 45 Brooklyn, Mrs. Orshaw, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13667)
  - IS 302 Dedication, Dec 17, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13745)
  - Sarah J Hale JHS Brooklyn Dedication, Teachers Lounge, Jan 28, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13818)
  - Fred Nauman -UFT College Scholarships, Feb 4, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13826)
  - Para-professional becomes Teacher 369 Armory, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13854)
  - Frontlash Exhibit & Award, Feb 22, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13868)
  - PS 148 Dedication, Mar 1, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13881)
  - PS 31 Gold Jubilee, Apr 26, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13960)
  - Carmella Nefi Luncheon, Apr 29, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13964)
  - IS 145 Mini School Opening, May 19, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14014)
  - Scholarship students [Names of each student written on negatives], May 20, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14017)
  - Dave Wittes Memorial, May 25, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14031)
  - Scholarship Awards, Jun 8, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14046)
  - PS 161 Bronx Awards Art, Jun 12, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14059)
  - Franklin K Lane HS, UFT Awards, George Altomare, Jun 29, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14075)
  - Scholarship Awards [UFT College Scholarship Fund], Apr 1, 1973 (Box 30, Item 15606)
  - Reception Commodore, May 23, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14361)
  - Scholarship awards, May 30, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14371)
  - African Exhibit [and ribbon cutting], Oct 17, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14455)
  - Scholarship Awards [Whitestone Photos], May 28, 1974 (Box 30, Item 14655)
- Series III: Chapters.
  - Secretaries petitions Board of Education, Jun 18, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7059)
  - Child Guidance Bureau, Mar 19, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7533)
  - Child Guidance Election, Apr 26, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7623)
  - Attendance Teachers, Dec 12, 1963 (Box 3, Item 8034)
  - Child Guidance, May 26, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8340)
  - Guidance Teachers at Maritime Union, Sep 10, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8535)
  - Substitute Teachers at Board of Education, Sep 15, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8538)
  - Guidance Teachers Washington Irving HS, Sep 19, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8534)
  - Secretaries Astor [Hotel], Apr 28, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8989)
  - School Secretaries, Oct 14, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9324)
  - School Secretaries George Washington Hotel, Jan 17, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9555)
  - Secretaries Retreat Tarrytown, May 7, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9893)
  - Guidance Group, Jan 23, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10254)
  - Guidance Counselors Contract Signing Board of Education, Mar 6, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10340)
  - Staten Island Chapter, Apr 15, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10439)
  - Bronx Chapter, Apr 15, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10438)
  - Voc[ational] Teachers Picket Board of Education, Jun 9, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10559)
  - Retired Teachers, May 14, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11216)
  - Guidance [Teachers], Sep 19, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11368)
  - Retired Teachers Marc Ballroom, Oct 15, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11422)
  - UFT Child Guidance Brooklyn, Oct 28, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11458)
  - Child Guidance Group, Check to Albert Shanker + Headshot, Bilingual Teachers, Jan 16, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11597)
  - Mrs. [Ruth] Melton - Homebound [teachers], Mar 13, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11712)
  - Para-Professionals PS 182 Brooklyn, Mar 27, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11748)
  - PS 123 Queens Para-Professionals [& students], Apr 11, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11770)
  - Retired Teachers, May 13, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11879)
  - Hollis, Board of Education Fantasy [?] East Para-Professionals, May 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11885)
  - Board of Education Para-Professionals, Jun 4, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11934)
  - Dante's Restaurant - Para-Professional, Jun 6, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11941)
  - Board of Education Para-Professionals, Jun 13, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11967)
  - Nominating Committee Guidance Counselors Inst. [?] [group photographs of men and women at official function, perhaps at a hotel], Jun 22, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11983)
  - Para-Professionals Election Brandeis, Jun 25, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11984)
  - School Secretaries Marc Ballroom, Sep 2, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12029)
  - Lab. Specs. & Techs, Sep 3, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12031)
  - Guidance Counselors George Washington Hotel, Sep 4, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12032)
  - Child Guidance at UFT, Sep 5, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12033)
  - Secretaries / Voc. H. S. / John Hill, Oct 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12113)
  - Para-Professionals [at work in classrooms with students], Oct 16, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12114)
  - Para-Professionals [meeting and front façade of UFT building]], Oct 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12123)
  - Para-Professionals Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 29, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12149)
  - Gladys Roth Para-Professional Brooklyn, Nov 10, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12187)
  - Board of Education Early Childhood com [?], Nov 17, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12202)
  - Para-Professionals Granada Hotel, Nov 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12223)
  - Para-Professionals - [Al] Shanker Meeting, Nov 24, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12231)
  - Board of Education Para-Professionals, Dec 19, 1969 (Box 10, Item 12299)
  - Para-Professionals [meeting], Jan 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12319)
  - Homebound Teachers, Jan 13, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12332)
  - Para-Professionals at Board of Education 110 Livingston, Jan 22, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12340)
  - Para-Professionals Marc Ballroom, Jan 28, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12361)
  - Secretaries Meeting, Jan 30, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12369)
  - Para-Professionals Counseling, Jan 30, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12371)
  - School Secretaries at Marc Ballroom, Feb 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12384)
  - Para-Professionals, Feb 25, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12409)
  - School Secretaries Meeting George Washington Hotel, Feb 26, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12411)
  - Para-Professionals Marc Ballroom, Mar 12, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12439)
  - Para-Professional Vote, Apr 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12525)
  - Union Leaders for Para-Professionals, Randolph, Gramercy Hotel, May 7, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12560)
  - Jamaica H.S. Guidance Counselor[s], May 20, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12608)
  - Bayard Rustin & Dave's [?] at Board Room & Headshots [talking to Para-Professionals], May 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12610)
  - HS of Fashion - Para-Professionals District Coordinators, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12676)
  - Guidance Counselors Board of Education [Brooklyn ?], Jun 19, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12696)
  - Para-Professional heads & election Waldorf, Jun 22, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12701)
  - Para-Professionals Examination H.S. Equivalency, Jun 27, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12709)
  - Para-Professionals Irving Plaza Voting, Aug 3, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12733)
  - Guidance Counselors Gramercy Hotel, Nov 5, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12875)
  - Para-Professionals at Marc Ballroom, Nov 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12900)
  - Secretaries [meeting], Nov 19, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12906)
  - Guidance Counselors & Para-Professional Executive Committee, Dec 9, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12952)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13015)
  - Secretaries Action Committee - HS of Art & Design, Jan 21, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13026)
  - PS 94 School Secretaries (office), Feb 1, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13045)
  - Bronx Boro Office - Para-Professionals Registration College, Feb 1, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13046)
  - Manhattan Office - Para-Professional Applications College, Feb 2, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13047)
  - Para-Professional Contract Signing - Board of Education, Mar 3, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13114)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Mar 9, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13136)
  - Kings County Comm. College Para-Pros., Mar 29, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13175)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13226)
  - Para-Professional Teacher PS 35, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13223)
  - Future Teachers, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13228)
  - Secretaries at Mrs. Robins, May 17, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13306)
  - Early Childhood Chairman Rose de Fuente, Eva Vigman, May 24, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13341)
  - Assigned Teachers UTO DeLeon [?], May 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13354)
  - UFT at PS 2 District 2 Para-Professional Meeting, Velma Hill, Frank Brown, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13344)
  - PS 94 Brooklyn Para-Professional - Paycuts[?] Party, Jun 15, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13398)
  - Guidance Counselors Marc Ballroom Gramercy Park, Jun 17, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13414)
  - Para-Professional - Velma Hill - Elected Reps - Marc Ballroom, Jun 18, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13412)
  - Early - childhood luncheon - La Bibliotheque, Jun 19, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13411)
  - Assigned Teacher Swear in, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13425)
  - Secretaries Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 7, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13518)
  - Executive Board Room Homebound Council, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13522)
  - Secretaries Committee, Edith Duffy, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13523)
  - School Secretaries headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Nov 10, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13618)
  - Para-Professional Elected Reps., Dec 16, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13746)
  - Para-Professional Meeting IS 131 Bronx, Jan 24, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13809)
  - Para-Professional Com. Brooklyn, Feb 10, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13832)
  - Para-professional becomes Teacher 369 Armory, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13854)
  - Gramercy Park Hotel Guidance Counselors, Mar 7, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13884)
  - Bronx Boro office emergency meeting of Chapter, May 5, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13975)
  - Guidance Counselors conference, May 24, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14026)
  - NY City Personnel Guidance Conference, Mar 9, 1973 (Box 29, Item 14252)
  - Laboratory Specialists, Washington Irving HS, Jun 13, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14394)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Jun 18, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14396)
- Series IV: Committees.
  - Grievance Committee, May 12, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6362)
  - Committee, Mar 21, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7541)
  - Pension Committee, Apr 26, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7624)
  - [Robert] Atkin[s] & committee, Apr 24, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8279)
  - Committee [?], Apr 12, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8968)
  - Contract Proposal Comm. Cent. HS, Sep 9, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10789)
  - Spring Luncheon Committee, Jan 8, 1968 (Box 6, Item 10987)
  - QuEST [Quality Educational Standards in Teaching] Comm., Sep 30, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12082)
  - Committees Para-Professionals [Roberta L. ] Fass/[Jacqueline F.] Lander GE grape [Teaching Unit on the "Struggle of the Farm Workers for Collective Bargaining".], Nov 24, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12233)
  - Committee Inspecting JHS Queens, Jan 27, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12354)
  - Elementary School Com., Nov 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12901)
  - QuEST Committee, Dec 8, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12946)
  - Guidance Counselors & Para-Professional Executive Committee, Dec 9, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12952)
  - Music Teachers Committee Meeting, Dec 11, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12960)
  - IS 142 Queens Comm., Dec 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12978)
  - J.H.S. Comm. [speaking to audience], Jan 7, 1971 (Box 16, Item 12994)
  - Citywide Emergency Committee Bayard Rustin, Feb 2, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13048)
  - HS Committee, Feb 25, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13103)
  - HS Committee - Bob Miller, Mar 9, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13129)
  - HS Committee, Mar 25, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13166)
  - Evaluation Committee, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13227)
  - Central Comm. HS Albert Shanker Speaking, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13217)
  - Committee Ret. Teachers, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13525)
  - JHS Committee Executive Board Room, Oct 14, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13531)
  - CRMD [Children with Retarded Mental Development] Committee, Oct 18, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13540)
  - Vocational HS Committee, Oct 21, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13556)
  - Spring Conferences Committee (Gramercy Park Hotel), Nov 4, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13596)
  - Special Education Committee, George Washington Hotel, Nov 16, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13628)
  - Music Committee, Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13647)
  - L I University Mayors Comm. [?] Hearing on Disabled, Jan 11, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13795)
  - Security Comm., Mar 2, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13880)
  - HS Committee Executive Board Room, Mar 23, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13917)
  - HS renovation [?] committees - Community College Comm., May 9, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13978)
  - Jr. HS Comm. Pare College, May 12, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13993)
  - At[tendance] HS Comm. [teachers at table], May 18, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14015)
  - Ed. Comm., May 4, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14325)
  - Glen Cove Spec. Ed. Comm., Oct 19, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14460)
- Series V: Conferences.
  - Teachers' Guild Union Conference Astor Hotel, Oct 4, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4349)
  - Teachers' Guild Annual Conference Father George Ford, Mar 7, 1959 (Box 2, Item 4750)
  - NY Teachers' Guild Annual Conference A. Philip Randolph Honored, Mar 5, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5489)
  - Annual Conference Justice William O. Douglass, Feb 23, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7484)
  - Out of town Teachers Conference George Washington Hotel, Mar 15, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8187)
  - Board of Education Conferences, Oct 11, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9308)
  - Spring Conference Group, Dec 11, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10944)
  - Tarrytown - Accountability, Jun 13, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12673)
  - District 19 Conference, Jul 9, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12717)
  - MES Conf. Tarrytown, Oct 31, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12861)
  - Spring Conference Display - Sessions - Awards (1st Day), Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13221)
  - Spring Conference (2nd Day), Apr 24, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13224)
  - Cocktail Party - luncheon Spring Conference (2nd Day), Apr 24, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13225)
  - Ed. Conf. PS 154 M, May 22, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13333)
  - Sandy Blair PS 95 Bronx End of Year Conference, May 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13342)
  - MES Conference PS 154, Jun 5, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13372)
  - IS 348 Brooklyn, broken into sub-school conference, Oct 13, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13524)
  - Security Conference District 17 Brooklyn, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13580)
  - Planning Conference, Julia Richmond HS, Dec 20, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13750)
  - MES State Conference, JHS All Day Conference, Jan 8, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13781)
  - New Rochelle Conference, May 10, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13989)
  - Guidance Counselors conference, May 24, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14026)
  - New Rochelle Annual Teachers Conference, May 26, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14033)
  - Board of Education Reading Conference [ ___ __ ?], May 25, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14365)
- Series VI: Contracts and Negotiations.
  - [Retirement Board], undated (Box 2, Item 7304)
  - Bargaining group Cayan - Homberg, Dec 6, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6683)
  - Manhattan Center ["Collective Bargaining for Teachers Democracy in Education." Dance/Social], Dec 21, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6718)
  - Bargaining at Board of Education, Feb 6, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6846)
  - Bargaining Office, Feb 13, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6773)
  - Delegate Assembly Contract, Sep 19, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7124)
  - Contract Signing - Board of Education (seated), Oct 18, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7191)
  - 1st Collective Bargaining Contract Signing (Cogen & Max J. Rubin), Oct 18, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7191)
  - Contract Signing Board of Education, Oct 18, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7191)
  - Contract Signing Board of Education James Donavon, Feb 10, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8127)
  - Board of Education Attendants Teachers contract signing, Mar 25, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8211)
  - Contract [?] Queens, May 6, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8299)
  - Board of Education Contract Signing, Jan 25, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8813)
  - Contract Negotiations Commodore Hotel, Sep 7, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9154)
  - Contract Signing, Nov 24, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9424)
  - Board of Education Welfare Fund Contract Signings, Feb 17, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9672)
  - Contract Signing [at Board of Education] Boro Hall, Mar 1, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9701)
  - Guidance Counselors Contract Signing Board of Education, Mar 6, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10340)
  - Contract Proposal Comm. Cent. HS, Sep 9, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10789)
  - District Negotiators Groups, Oct 17, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10839)
  - Negotiations Committee Board of Education, Jan 14, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11775)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum, May 13, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11876)
  - Board of Education Contract Signing [?], Dec 16, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12286)
  - Functional Chapters Contract Signing Board of Education, May 13, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12585)
  - Para-Professional Contract Signing - Board of Education, Mar 3, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13114)
  - TRU contract signing, Jun 16, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13410)
- Series VII: Dedicated Days/Weeks/Celebrations.
  - IS 293 Brooklyn Puerto Rican Night, undated (Box 24, Item 13629)
  - Negro History Panel, Jul 8, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10007)
  - Meeting Afro-American, May 18, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10503)
  - PS 130 Spr[ing] [African-American history day], Feb 9, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11050)
  - Art Exhibit Dr. King, Jun 4, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11261)
  - K 25 Afro American History Exhibit, Feb 12, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11657)
  - Afro History, Feb 17, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11663)
  - PS 129 [Dr. Martin Luther] King Museum, Feb 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11675)
  - Puerto Rican Festival PS 327, Nov 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12215)
  - PS 304 Bedford / Stuyvesant Food & [Black Heritage] Displays, Feb 11, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12388)